["The Heart of Me" by Miike Snow playing]
[woman] I'm Luke's roommate.
When people look at Luke, they think
he's this player type of person,
but he actually isn't. He's very Southern.
He's actually really caring and sweet.
♪ You took the yellow diamond spears ♪
♪ And turned it on its head ♪
Luke and I met in college,
and he's very sexy.
Luke always goes for very pretty girls,
but he likes someone
he can take home to Mama.
-How's it going?
-[man] Luke?
Yep.
♪ To the heart of me ♪
[woman] He looks like a model.
He's got the walk. He's got the talk,
but Luke can also be a little mysterious.
♪ To the heart of me ♪
♪ Because I can't believe ♪
Victoria?
-Yeah.
-I'm Luke.
-Hi!
-Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
-I'm excited.
-You look great.
-Thank you. You look really great, too.
-Thank you.
-Are you hungry?
-Yeah. Oh, my gosh.
Always hungry, constantly.
-You want to grab a drink at the bar?
-Yeah, definitely.
-Hi.
-Kate?
-How are you? Yeah.
-I'm Luke.
-Luke? Handshake, kiss?
-Nice to meet you.
What's going on?
-Thanks for meeting me.
-Yeah.
[both laughing]
-Ooh, they have sake.
-Sake fan?
-Take it hot or cold?
-Cold.
-Do you like it hot?
-I like hot sake sometimes.
-I prefer cold.
-Yeah.
I don't know if they have hot sake here,
anyway, but cold sake's still really good.
[laughing] Yeah. Yeah.
Well, it turned out
that you're good looking, so that's good.
Thank you.
-[laughs]
-So how old are you?
-Twenty-seven.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
-How old do I look?
-Twenty three.
-Okay, good.
-I don't know. You're--
-I'm 28.
-Twenty-eight? You look great.
-Thank you.
You are very handsome.
Thank you. So are you.
-Oh!
-Yeah! [laughs]
[laughs]
-Where are you from?
-I grew up in North Carolina,
but I've been in New York
for about four years now.
-How about you?
-I'm from Colombia.
-Okay.
-I've been here nine years already.
I know my accent is strong.
Yeah, I could kind of tell an accent
a little at first,
but now it's much stronger
-now that I know.
-I know.
-I'm still working on my English.
-Okay.
I am from Massachusetts originally.
I'm a Masshole.
A Masshole?
-You've heard that.
-I've never heard that before.
-How've you never heard that before?
-I don't know.
-I need that as a tramp stamp. [laughs]
-That's hilarious.
That's so good. [laughs]
Did you move here
straight after college or...
Well, I went to school in Florida,
in Orlando.
-What school?
-University of Central Florida.
Oh, my God. I went to Florida Southern.
It's smaller, you probably
have no idea where that is,
but we found a commonality.
-Yeah.
-That's it.
If you want to text your mom right now,
you can totally do that.
-"I think I'm in love."
-Yeah?
I'll do something creepy.
"Ma!
Ma, I met the one!"
-Where in the city do you live?
-50th and 9th,
-around there.
-Really?
I'm right there. I'm on 50th and 8th.
-Same neighborhood?
-Same, yeah.
-I'm in Gramercy.
-Oh, cool.
-That's an excellent area.
-It is.
-I'm obsessed with it.
-I love Irving.
Irving's one of my favorite streets.
-Do you have a favorite restaurant?
-I work in food, so that's like...
-I can't even imagine.
-Yeah, I know.
-How about you?
-Jersey girl.
All right.
But not like Jersey Shore though.
Like, that's not Jersey.
-Why not? No, I know.
-They aren't from Jersey.
-They give Jersey a bad rap.
-They do.
-Do you work in the city?
-I work in recruiting.
-That's awesome.
-So, yeah.
I am in FiDi, right on the corner
of, like, the New York Stock Exchange.
-It's crazy down there.
-Yeah.
I start every morning by almost murdering
six people with the selfie sticks.
I just want to charge through
and smash four down.
Especially on a Monday morning.
I'm just like...
That's so funny.
-So what'd you--
-We're having a very strange conversation.
This is par for the course with me.
You should be happy we haven't gotten
into weirder territory yet.
I am so excited.
-Gird your loins.
-Wait. [laughs]
Saddle up.
[laughing]
-Can we toast?
-Yeah.
Yeah. Nice meeting you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Looking forward to a good date.
To the first blind date of my life.
-All right. I'll cheers to that. Me too.
-Hope you're not a serial killer.
-Cheers to us and cheers to Jersey.
-Cheers to Jersey.
All right.
Cheers.
It's good you looked me in the eye.
It's bad luck if you don't.
They say you'll have, like, bad sex
for, like, ten years or something.
See, I always look in the eye.
Always do that because you don't want
to be screwed on that end of things.
-Or not screwed. Yeah, so...
-Exactly.
[chuckles]
What's in yours?
Uh... [clears throat]
[Kate laughs]
It's really interesting.
-Do you want to try it? You like spicy?
-Yeah.
I die for spicy.
-Do you like spicy?
-I do. Yeah.
It's good.
-I kind of like that.
-Yeah.
-What is this?
-[Kate] Um, like, a margarita.
Oh.
-You're like, "I'm good."
-Yeah, I think, uh... [laughs]
You had one, you had them all, right?
-I thought it was going to be a special.
-Yeah.
-Um, so you moved here nine years ago.
-Yes.
It was with family?
Um, so. It was, uh...
I met my, um, ex-husband here.
-Ah, okay.
-I got married when I was very young.
I was working as a waiter
and he was my client,
but he didn't speak Spanish,
and I didn't speak English.
So it was a little bit different,
and then we actually went on a date.
We were just
looking at each other, like...
-And just smiling.
-Yeah.
Actually, I did that same thing.
I met a girl in Ecuador
when I was down there.
The only way we could talk
-was Google Translate.
-Yeah.
I know it's a little crazy,
but it just worked out like that.
-Yeah.
-You ready to eat?
-Sure.
Okay.
Vámonos.
-Let me get the chair for you.
-Thank you.
There you go.
Thank you so much.
Jacket's coming off.
Yeah.
That sounds...
-hot.
-[both laughing]
Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
-All right.
Hello!
-Sorry I'm so late.
-Hi.
-I'm Ashley. Nice to meet you.
-I'm Luke.
-How are you?
-Nice to meet you. Good.
Thank you.
Oh, my God. Traffic was so crazy.
[laughing] Yeah, right?
So crazy.
So the first thing we're gonna do
is get shots.
-Hell, yeah.
-We're gonna get shots.
Okay, so tell me...
-Tell me everything.
-Yeah.
-You want to know everything right now?
-Not right now.
[laughs]
So, what are you feeling?
Should we share a couple things?
-Are you allergic to nuts or anything?
-No.
-Do you like peanuts?
-Do you--
-I don't have allergies.
-Okay.
-I do like peanuts.
-So... I do, too. So can we ask for extra?
-Sure, yeah. So you love peanuts?
-Cool.
Well, it's good 'cause it gives
a little crunch, a little life to it.
It's noodles and then a crunch.
I need the crunch.
I'm glad you know a lot about food.
-Are you, though?
-You're gonna have to... I am.
-You can help me with the menu.
-Oh, ordering is like my expertise.
-Okay. I trust you.
-I like to think it's a talent of mine.
Yeah.
-Knowing what's good. Sixth sense.
-That's a difficult thing.
Yeah.
[Betty] Are you hungry?
-Very, yeah.
-Very?
-You?
-Yeah.
-I eat a lot.
-[laughing] Yeah?
Me, too. Yeah.
-There's nothing that I don't like.
-So how you look like this, then?
Got to... You work out. I like to run.
-So, we're so close to the park.
-Me too. Yeah.
-Where do you run?
-I have a natural loop that I do--
Around the lake?
-Yes, yeah.
-Me too.
-The reservoir, mornings.
-I've never seen you.
If I see you, I'd be like,
"Hey, excuse me."
I'm pretty sure I would remember, too.
-You look amazing, in such great shape.
-Thank you.
Are you, like, a petite guy?
Do you like a girl that's a little more
thickish, slim, thick?
-Slim thick?
-Slim think is a thing.
-That's like a thin waist with--
-With, like, a little butt.
-Yeah.
-I got shredded this last year.
Like, I went, like, vegan,
and I kickboxed every day,
and I was just like,
-like a 12-pack.
-Yeah?
-That's awesome.
-Yeah.
-It's terrifying.
-Not the ass-beating part, but--
-Yeah. Getting in shape is cool.
-You're into it. You know it.
-[woman] Are you guys ready to order?
-I think it's gonna be a tag-team effort,
-'cause we didn't look.
-What are you feeling?
We're gonna do the shrimp spring rolls,
we're gonna do an order of edamame
and then we're gonna share the pad thai
with extra peanuts and...
Chicken.
-Can we get everything out at once though?
-Yes, of course.
-Perfect. Thank you.
-[woman] Mm-hmm.
That was easy.
I like how you take the lead.
[laughs]
So, tell me more things about you.
I'm in real estate, yeah.
-Real estate?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-So I'm on the broker side.
My main focus is
working with buyers and sellers.
You're such a real-estate guy, too.
Um...
-You know?
-That could go--
-Like, you're just very--
-So, I mean, real estate. Sure, yeah.
So did you come here
wanting to do real estate or...
-Not really, no.
-Yeah.
I wanted to move to New York.
-It's always been a dream to live here.
-Yeah.
And so I basically quit my job in Florida,
like, doing finance
and moved up here and just tried
to figure out what I wanted to do,
and real estate just kept...
-coming up, and--
-Wait, you moved here without...
like, without a job or anything?
-You freeballed it?
-Pretty much, yeah.
You were, like...
Yeah, I freeballed it, straight up, yeah.
All right. [laughs]
But, okay, so where are you in the process
of your New York dreams right now?
I don't know. I feel like it's just been,
like, upward progression since I got here.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Like, the city definitely
teaches you a lot.
No, this is a place that, like,
breaks your dreams,
and then you remake new ones
out of the pieces of your old dreams.
This is where you're supposed
to go for dreams.
-I know.
-It's where you make your dreams.
Remind me what you do.
I am working at a finance tech start-up,
which is great because I can barely
turn on my laptop, so it's very ironic.
[both laugh]
[woman] Here's the drink menu.
So this guy can't stand my personality
and wants another tequila shot,
so I'm just gonna do it with him
so it's less awkward.
-[woman] Okay.
-Yeah. Thank you.
[laughs]
So do you go dancing a lot?
-I don't go dancing.
-Do you know how to dance?
I don't know how.
-Can you hop to a beat?
-Not a great dancer.
-I can...
-Two-step?
-work it a little bit.
-Yeah.
-How about you?
-Oh, I'm a good dancer.
-You are?
-Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
-I'll take lessons.
-Yeah.
We'll have to go dancing.
Yeah. So what do you do?
I work at Estee Lauder in beauty,
and then I just started a nonprofit, too.
-That's great.
-Yeah.
-[woman] Food's here.
-Oh, yay.
-Are you guys sharing?
-Yes.
-And the best thing on the menu.
-[Kate] Wow, really? Ooh.
Oh, man. So exciting.
-[Victoria] Wow, it's your pad thai!
-See? Look at that.
Look how pretty it is!
I might just go fingers.
Yeah, do it.
I'm gonna stick with the chopsticks, but--
-[laughs] I'm just kidding.
-That's so--
-I'm joking.
-Actually, yeah.
I'd love to see you use your chopsticks.
My skills are... they're good.
-Okay.
-Let me tell you.
Actually, you're right. They are.
-Yeah?
-Mm-hmm.
-How about you?
-Oh, mine are amazing.
One time I had a person comment
on how good they were.
You hold them way at the end?
-No, I just, like, lift it up like a boss.
-Awesome.
Oh, sh... You kind of whipped them out
like a professional, so now I'm nervous.
Oh, my God,
you're holding them at the end, too?
-You're like a real pro.
-You have to--
Yeah. I mean, I can catch flies
and the whole deal.
[both laugh]
-I'm using the fork.
-Go for it.
I have no qualms about how I eat.
-I chew very loud.
-Yeah?
And that's because I enjoy the food.
I don't care.
So you-- [laughs]
[Tiffany giggles]
Literally, my sister will be like,
"Why do you chew like that?"
-Oh, you, like, smack your lips and just--
-Maybe, because it's flavorful.
-Does that help you enjoy the food?
-Yeah.
You taste that food
with more flavorfulness mouthness.
You got to go like...
[loudly smacks lips]
Because you can taste it.
Taste the spices.
-Wait, how do you do it again?
-I don't do that in real life.
That was just to show you.
All right. Here we go.
Just taste it.
Just open, breathe.
[smacking]
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah, yeah!
-Mmm.
-How you loving it? So much better.
-Is it?
-[laughs]
-It tastes so much better.
-You are who you are.
You do what you like and you...
you just, like, want to enjoy things
the way that it is.
[smacks lips] This prosecco is so bubbly.
-Wow!
-[laughing]
That's great.
So tell me about your dating life.
I want to know all about it.
-All about my dating life?
-Yeah.
Yeah, so...
the last relationship I was in
ended eight or nine months ago.
-Mm-hmm.
-And, like, since then,
I've been consistently dating...
-and just going--
-Have you?
-Yeah, just--
-It never happens...
-for me.
-Really?
Ever. Never.
I'm not even kidding.
-You're so beautiful. That's surprising.
-Thank you.
-I know. I think I have the--
-You're like, "I know.
I'm, like, really hot, and these dudes
aren't coming up to me. What's going on?"
-I mean, I go out.
-Yeah.
I put myself... It just doesn't happen.
So... are you approaching guys?
-No. Oh, God, no. Me? Approach someone?
-Why not?
-Unh-unh.
I really don't. It's just not my thing.
What would I say to a guy? Like, "Hi!"
"What's your name?"
-You can start there.
-True.
You got to go for it sometimes, you know?
What type of guys do you like?
I like someone who's, like,
into what they do and is, like...
passionate about their job
and is intelligent.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, just like the core qualities.
Yeah. And then I feel like guys
that I normally go for also, like...
love, like, being social.
Yeah, of course. Especially in New York.
-Totally.
-It's the main thing to do.
-That's why we live here.
-Yeah.
-I would definitely agree.
Yeah. [laughs]
Um...
So, I mean, you've been with somebody,
you know, like, been married, divorced.
So, like, what are you looking for now?
[sighs]
Let me finish this first.
[laughs] No. Um...
To be honest, I just want...
I just want love.
Yeah, 100%.
-I don't want, like, games or--
-You want a...
-deep connection.
-Yes.
Connection, chemistry, love.
I am all about feelings.
Yeah.
Little parentheses here.
When I first introduced myself,
I got distracted by this,
so I didn't get your name.
-[laughing] Sorry.
-Oh, my name?
-Yeah.
-Oh, it's okay.
-Little parentheses.
-Yeah.
-It's Luke.
-Luke? Okay.
-And yours is Becky, right?
-Nope.
No, I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding.
It's Betty. I know. I'm joking.
You got me. [laughs]
I never asked you.
You don't have any kids, right?
-No.
-Okay, just making sure.
-Do you?
-No, I don't.
-Yes.
-But, um... I want a lot of kids.
-Like, that's something that--
-Like, how many?
I don't know.
As many as I can handle, I guess.
-Okay. It was very nice--
-I would... yeah.
Really?
It's not something you should talk of
on the first date, but...
Yeah, that is a little
deeper conversation, but...
-Um, I mean, I definitely want a family.
-That's good.
-And--
-Well, family's important.
Yeah, it is.
And, like, finding somebody that you...
you know, can share,
like, an attraction with--
You're going with the three C's:
compatibility, chemistry, and connection.
They really revert back to everything.
-Yeah.
-So just be yourself.
[loudly smacks lips]
Hi. I'm Tiffany.
[Tiffany laughs]
"I'm Luke. Nice to meet you."
-Just be yourself.
-Yeah.
How are you single?
I don't understand this.
-What do you mean?
-You seem such a great girl.
Look how I eat. [laughs]
-So many girls just don't--
-You're lucky to be with me right now.
-Just so you know.
-I feel very--
-I feel very lucky right now.
-You should feel lucky. You should.
Yeah, I think-- I think one
of the main reasons I'm single now
is because I've been more
on a personal journey myself
with getting to a place where I want to be
and where I feel...
um...
like I can bring someone into my life
and, you know,
create a family with this person
and create a life with someone else.
I feel like the last couple of years,
especially since I moved to New York,
I've just been so, like, go-go-go 24/7
that I don't even think about dating.
Yeah.
But, like, I'm-- I'm working on it,
you know? Life is too short.
Yeah, for sure.
You want to get out of here?
-Yeah. Let's do it.
-Sound good?
Look at that.
Oh, wow. Full moon.
-Yeah. That's beautiful.
-So beautiful, right?
-It's so beautiful.
-I know.
[Tiffany] See that full moon?
-[Luke] Wait, hold on.
-[Tiffany] Wait. Do you see the full moon?
-We took tequila shots earlier, but--
-I know. I know.
-That is a full moon tonight.
-That was good.
-So you were right. Yeah.
Let's walk.
Wow!
-I know.
-Um...
All right, so...
I'm so thankful
for this full moon right now.
[both laugh]
-That requires a sexy dance.
-[both laugh]
Yeah, I think so.
-Okay. Let's do it, then.
-Yeah.
Here we go.
Got to put the purse down
and everything.
-Okay.
-[laughing] Yeah.
So we're gonna dance salsa.
-We're gonna dance salsa right now?
-Yeah. You can grab me.
-Okay. Like this?
-Yeah.
-Oh, there you go.
-Yeah?
-Yes.
-Okay.
And then, um...
one, two, three.
One, two, three.
Oh, you see? I can teach you--
-Oh, you're good.
-I'm a fast learner, baby.
-I can tell.
-Yeah.
-And then like this. And then like that.
-Okay.
-One, two, three...
-It's a lot in the hips, right?
-Yes.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. And then we just--
-Okay.
Like that?
Dun... dun, dun.
Dun, dun, dun.
Yes.
And then, like this.
-You got me.
-There we go.
-And then we go a little bit like this.
-Mm-hmm.
Little bit, little bit...
-Then, little bit.
-Oh, my gosh.
-You're a killer.
-[laughing]
It's just-- [laughing]
I have to walk this off.
-Now you...
-[laughs]
You're getting me excited over here.
[Luke laughs]
So this was your, like, first pure blind?
-Pure blind date. Yeah.
-What'd you think?
-Um... what do you--
-Would you do it again?
-Would you do a pure blind date again?
-Would I go on a date with you again?
-Obviously the answer's yes, but, like...
-Yeah. You're amazing.
[laughs]
How about you?
Yeah, I guess so.
-It wasn't the worst date I've been on.
-Well, I'm glad to hear that.
I'm very surprised by you.
-Why?
-Because, I mean, you first walk in,
and, like, obviously, you're gorgeous.
You're so beautiful, you know,
but you're also... you're very deep.
[Betty laughs]
[Betty] You're so sweet.
[softly] That's right.
-[Luke] All right. Let's keep walking.
-[both laugh]
[Betty] Perfect night.
[Luke] It is a perfect night.
[Ashley] Tonight was fun.
-[Luke] Yeah, it was.
-I don't think we're soulmates,
-but--
-That's--
You know, sometimes, dates,
it's, like, you find out
-you're not right for each other, but--
-Exactly.
You find someone else through
the connection and that's what it's about.
I had an amazing time with you
and I know we'll be friends.
-[Luke] Yeah.
-[Ashley] I'm gonna call my Lyft.
-But I'll see you soon.
-Yeah. Okay. Sounds good.
-Bye! Get home safe!
-All right. Bye-bye.
-This is cute.
-Look at this.
-Got a little fireplace.
-Look at this. It's romantic.
-You pulled out all the stops tonight.
-You like that?
[laughs]
-Thanks for coming to get a drink with me.
-No, of course. I'm having so much fun.
-Good. Me too.
-Really.
-Cheers.
-Last one.
-Last drink.
Yeah, we said it at the same time.
So, what's your, uh...
what's your dating life like?
There are so many options in the city.
There are so many options,
but sometimes, I think that people...
-swipe past the best thing out there.
-Yeah.
They're constantly looking
for something amazing
and there's something amazing sitting
right in front of them, and they're like,
not focused on it. You know what I mean?
Like, they're just looking
for the next thing,
and then maybe one day, they wake up
down the road and they're like, "Uh."
-Yeah.
-Like...
"Wow, the third swipe in. That was it,
and instead I just kept going."
Right. Because you wanted to see
what else was out there.
Exactly.
This is gonna be
one of my favorite stories to tell.
[laughs]
To our grandchildren, right?
-Oh.
-Is that-- [laughs]
-[chuckles] Cheers for that.
-Yeah?
[Betty laughs]
-All right. There we go.
-Yeah.
[exhales]
-It's, like, getting so late.
-Yeah.
-[laughs]
-I'm getting so sleepy.
I know.
-Let's sleep here. Should we sleep here?
-Yeah.
-It's a very comfortable couch, right?
-Okay. Tired. See?
Let's just sleep here then.
You're so tired.
Thanks so much for everything.
-Yeah.
-Definitely.
Are we sleeping now?
-Almost.
-Yeah.
-What are you thinking?
Um...
I don't know. We should probably--
-We should probably get out of here soon.
-Yeah.
-Should we go?
Okay.
-You ready?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
[Victoria walks into door]
[Victoria chuckling]
Oh, wait hold on.
[both laughing]
There you go.
I just walked face-first into that.
[horns honking in the distance]
Let me haul up my pants.
-[grunts]
-Yep, there you go.
Pure class all the way. Keep going.
I can't believe--
So you're always this fun.
This is who you are.
Like, I feel like you're subbing in "fun"
for, like, "strange,"
-but, yes, I am. I am like this 24/7.
-It's incredible.
Why? Why, you don't meet a lot of...
-random women on blind dates out at bars?
-I can say this with 100% accuracy.
I've never met anybody
like you before, ever.
[both laugh]
I'm just telling you.
I like to be fat, and I like to eat food,
and I like to be, like,
not socially acceptable.
-Just so you know.
-Yeah.
[loudly smacks lips]
You just smack your lips,
-taste the food as good as you can.
-Taste the food.
Taste it.
It's, like, nice to go out
with a foodie that knows
what stuff to order at places.
-[laughs]
-[Like] Um... [laughs]
-It was really nice to meet you.
-You as well.
But, um...
Yeah.
-We should hang out again. It'll be fun.
-Yeah.
Um...
Yeah.
I think I would enjoy seeing you again.
We should exchange numbers and--
-Definitely. Yeah. For sure.
-Let's do that.
So, what is your name again?
-Come on.
-[Betty laughs]
-I got you.
-We have jokes now.
Here we go.
No, seriously, though,
like, why are you single?
Why am I single?
I'm actually recently single.
Also, no one can handle
this heat, obviously.
I'm, like, falling.
[Luke laughs]
Don't.
[laughing] Where are we going right now?
-We're at my apartment.
-Yeah.
Yeah.
-I had a really fun night with you.
-I know. Thank you.
Okay. All right.
-I had fun. Thank you for everything.
-I had fun with you, too.
-I'll talk to you again.
-Okay.
[door closes]
[exhales]
Can we just, like, take a U-turn
and head to the nearest chapel?
His roofies are gonna kick in soon,
so I'm taking him--
I want to marry her
when I have the chance.
-He's catching me on a good night.
-Yeah.
-So he better lock it down or I'm gone.
-All right.
-It's your lucky night.
-I feel very lucky, actually.
-Well, we both live pretty close, so...
-[Betty] Yeah.
Maybe we'll just both get out together?
Yeah?
-Yeah? Okay.
-Let's see.
Gracias.
["Higher" by The Naked and Famous playing]
♪ Like we understood ♪
♪ Made with adrenaline ♪
♪ Seeping out through the skin ♪
♪ Like only lovers could ♪
♪ Here's where we begin ♪
♪ Time is the medicine ♪
♪ To heal these needs that only... ♪
Victoria.
-Hi!
-How are you?
[Victoria squeals, laughs]
So good to see you again. You look great.
-You look great, too.
-Yeah.
I'm happy you wanted to meet me again
after our first date.
Oh, you're game for round two?
I thought I might have scared you.
-I'm just gonna grab us a cab real quick.
-Okay.
Oh, my gosh. You look so good.
-You look good, too. You clean up well.
-Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Can you take the bridge up here, please?
-So I have something really fun planned.
-Oh, man.
-I can't tell you 'till we get there.
-Let's do this thing.
♪ Higher, higher ♪
♪ Higher, higher, higher ♪
♪ Tonight, we raise the dead ♪
♪ Tonight, we bury this in ♪
♪ Fire, fire ♪
♪ Under the shape of years ♪
♪ And the weight that brought us here ♪
♪ Better believe the sea of changes ♪
♪ Leave no reason to confess ♪
♪ And raise our voices ♪
♪ Higher, higher ♪